Guide to the George Gavras collection, 1967-1999.
Gavras, George collection
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
George Gavras collection, 1967-1999.
4753
Gavras, George
1 cubic foot.
Correspondence, Memorabilia, Printed Materials
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Includes newspaper articles and magazines concerning running; meet results and awards.
ORGANIZATIONAL HISTORY
Gavras was one of the four original Finger Lakes Runners Club members listed on the club charter. He was a competitive masters runner who competed on a Finger Lakes Runners Club masters team all over the United States and in Europe and continued to run into his 80's.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Includes newspaper articles and magazines concerning running; meet results and awards.
SUBJECTS
Names:
Gavras, George; Finger Lakes Runners Club
Subjects:
Running.; Running--Training.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
CONTAINER LIST
- Articles Written by George, Various (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Articles written about George, Various (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Photos of George (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Groton 6 Mile Race, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Masters Mile, 1968-1980 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Ithaca 5 & 10, 1984 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Masters Running, 1977-1994 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Club History, 1970-1981 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- U.S. Masters International Track Team, 1971-1972 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Boston Marathon, 1970-1983 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Race Numbers and Journals (Box 1, Folder 11)
- International Races, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Finger Lakes Marathon, 1970-1981 (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Misc. Course Data (Box 1, Folder 14)
- Misc. note and letter from George, 1968- (Box 1, Folder 15)
- Logo (Box 1, Folder 16)
- Race Articles, 1971-1999 (Box 1, Folder 17)
- Long Distance Log Magazines, 1968-1971 (Box 1, Folder 18)
- Distance Running News Magazines, 1967-1970 (Box 1, Folder 19)
- Running Times Magazines, 1977-1988 (Box 1, Folder 20)
- Sports Illustrated Magazines, 1971-1982 (Box 1, Folder 21)
- Runners World Magazines, 1975-1978 (Box 1, Folder 22)
- Track and Field News Magazines, 1969-1971 (Box 1, Folder 23)
- Misc. Race Results, 1969-1990 (Box 1, Folder 24)
- Misc. Race Awards (Box 1)